{
    "subject": "resource/How_Green_Was_My_Valley_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/John_Ford",
    "human_readable": "The film 'How Green Was My Valley' was directed by John Ford.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9726410508155823,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'How Green Was My Valley'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.932959258556366,
            "question": "Is 'How Green Was My Valley' a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7339452505111694,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by John Ford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7261688709259033,
            "question": "Name a film directed by John Ford."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6306719779968262,
            "question": "When was 'How Green Was My Valley' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6127498745918274,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'How Green Was My Valley' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4738761782646179,
            "question": "Are there any other famous films directed by John Ford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42954131960868835,
            "question": "Was John Ford an actor or a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38776296377182007,
            "question": "What awards did 'How Green Was My Valley' win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27469339966773987,
            "question": "What are some common themes in John Ford's films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'How Green Was My Valley' was directed by John Ford.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5587_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What awards did 'How Green Was My Valley' win?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5587_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was John Ford an actor or a director?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5587_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other famous films directed by John Ford?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5587_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5587_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5587_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5587_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5587_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5587_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5587_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5587_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5587_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5587_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5587_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that the movie \"How Green Was My Valley\" was indeed directed by John Ford. There is no contradictory information provided in any of the documents, so the triple can be confirmed as correct based on the given context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently state that \"How Green Was My Valley\" was directed by John Ford, making the statement in the query correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}